Bun, bun, bun ♪
Ahh! I’m a bird. I like to fly and spread out my wings.
Ow!
[Chuckles]
[Snoring]
Big bah bunny, big bah bunny ♪
What? What’s that? Ooh, it’s morning.
Oh boy. Yay! I’m awake!
Oh boy. Hey, ahh...
I like mornings. Oh man, I really have an itch in my ass.
Ahh. That feels good.
What is that smell?
Ooh... It’s flowers.
They’re like crack cocaine.
Ohh ohh...
That feels good.
• Hey, what's up with that?
• It’s a butterfly! Oh, boy. Let me grab it.
What a pretty – oh!
Uh? What the?
Hey, it’s an apple.
Where’d that come from?
Oh, must have come from up there.
Silly trees killing butterflies.
Oh, that’s a tasty apple. That’s a tasty apple.
But I’m still kind of sad.
• Stupid rabbit. I will get back at him.
• It’s a good apple. It’s just not as good when there's no – what the?
What? I thought it died! Oh, well, that’s good. It's still alive.
I'm going to chase it like a little kid.
• Ahh! There's a rabbit chasing me! Get away!
• Oh, it’s a butterfly.
• What a big fat thing!
• What a pretty butterfly.
What the? Where’d it go?
I’m too stupid to find it. ’Cause I’m trapped.
• Look at that. It’s a butterfly.
Oh, if I could just reach – ahh!
• Hmm. I wonder where it went.
I'm going to walk over here.
• Ha-ha! I have a plan.
• Nope. Nothing over here.
• Here’s Frankie!
Look over there! Get him!
• Ow!
Hey, what was that?
That wasn’t very nice.
• Hey, get him again.
• I’m going to throw this nut at him.
• Now!
• Oh, I dodged that. That was a good one.
Oh my. That could have been – ow!
Oh! Ow! That one really hurt.
• Uh-oh. What have we here?
It’s a little innocent butterfly.
• I'm a butterfly, I’m a butterfly.
• I'm going to crush it with a stone.
Crush! Ha-ha!
• No, how could you? Ah...
• Hey what’s that?
• I have a dead butterfly.
Ooh, I got a butterfly.
• What the?
No, I can’t fly.
I bet I can fly. I bet I can fly.
That is a spikey.
• What the?
Oh crap.
That's not good.
Those are some mean rodents.
Those are some really mean rodents.
What am I going to do? I’m gonna... Ooh, I have an idea.
I'm going to beat ’em up ’cause I am big.
Hey look! It's.. It’s a vine!
I could use something like this. I don't know... Yes, yes!
♪♪♪
Ooh, that’s embarrassing...
• Ha-ha
Ha-ha! Hey boys!
Maybe he’s in the forest.
We saw him run into the forest, maybe. We’re still in doubt.
• I'm following you boss.
• Could be in here.
I look left. I look right. Everywhere, I look around.
• I’ll get those rascal rodents!
I think I smell.. bunny.
Yup, there he is. I smelt something.
He is right around here.
Oh, that’s a big log!
★!
• Oh. Maybe he’s around here.
Oh. It’s very dark in here.
• Hey, Mr. Chinchilla. Get over there.
Move it!
That’s better.
• Oh... I’m flying!
• Ho-ho-ho, I showed that chinchilla.
• Oh, what the—? What are you doing here?
• What an ugly bird. I’ll kill you again.
• I hope that I don't get hit by a nut. That would suck.
Ow!
• There he is. The stupid rabbit.
Look at me!
I'm actually a flying squirrel!
I am flying.
• I wonder where that flying squirrel is.
He can't be behind me.
• I will do something to him.
I don't know what.
I will attack him using my...
My uh... I figure it out later.
♪♪♪
• Hey Mr. Flying Squirrel, look below!
• Look down—oh! What? What?
Tree.
Ah, spikes, no—
Grab on branch— Oh...
That was a close one.
Luckily... stick.
• Boo!
• Uh oh.
• I got you now, you little bastard.
♪♪♪
Ooh, what a nice summer day!
I’m just standing here – oh, it's a butterfly
I love butterflies.
They’re so nice.
And it's nice having a nice flying squirrel kite.
• What the f···!
I’m a kite that—
Ooh. Maybe I should make a silly face for no reason.
♪♪♪
• Copyright infringement ♪
We like to rip things off
Names...
This is the sound names make...
Who can read all those things?
Paulo... Diech... I'm terrible—sorry—at—
Oh wait, there's one I know. Timothy Vegdahl.
That's my little brother.
Yes! Hi Tim! You're awesome.
And there's the most important name.
♪♪♪
• Hey! What the—
Wait a second. There's something back there.
I'm gonna back up.
Hey! It looks like a flying squirrel!
• What the heck?
• I love to poo on flying squirrels.
Ahh!